this is our vliw target market quiz
solution so the question was what is vlw
best for among these three options we
already know that vlaw is best for
things where the compiler can figure the
program out
adding many numbers together is a very
easy thing for the compiler to figure
out typically we are talking about a
small loop with very well controlled
dependencies and so on in contrast
figuring out the best path in a maze
typically involves a lot of decisions
and then we will have to do a lot of
things conversions and so on so it's
going to be relatively inefficient
because a lot of the instructions that
we do are going to be predicated out
and then counting elements in a linked
list is going to have probably a lot of
load instructions some of them will miss
some of them are not so our compiler
scheduling will be greatly affected by
the cache misses and so on so this is
probably the best
scenario for a vliw followed probably by
something like this and it's unlikely to
do well on something like this